布村影视字幕组 www.bnemv.com 原创翻译
欢迎更多小伙伴加入
翻译｜立群　Ann　十二月　Jane　嘟嘟宝贝
校对｜不敢接电话的小兔纸
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
女士们，先生们，晚上好，这已经是到西雅图的最后一段路了
Good evening. ladies and gentlemen. We are on our final approach for Seattle.
目前天气状况良好，有些许东风
The weather is fair. with winds out of the east.
地表温度二十摄氏度
The temperature on the ground. 68 degrees.
我们全体机组人员在这里
On behalf of our cabin crew and us here on the flight deck.
谢谢大家与我们一起乘坐这次航班
we'd like to thank you for flying with us tonight.
睡不着真是能折磨死人
Life sucks when you can't sleep.
哦，说来听听
Yeah. tell me about it.
有些时候聊聊天比较好
Sometimes it's good to talk.
好吧
Okay.
这听起来很疯狂
This is gonna sound crazy.
但你听说过一种看完就会死的录像带吗？
but you ever hear about the videotape that kills you after you watch it?
我在一次聚会上，我遇到了一个来自西雅图的女孩
Well. I'm at this party and I meet this girl from Seattle.
我们很投缘
We totally hit it off.
第二天，她寄给我一个录像带，上面写着“看我”
The next day she sends me this video that says. "Watch me."
于是我找到一个录像机
So. I find a VCR.
开始看
watch it.
但它的画面…
but the images on it...
看完录像带的那一刻，我的电话突然响了
The second it was over. my phone rings.
对方是个女生说我将会在七天后死亡
And this girl says I'm gonna die in seven days.
也就是今天
That was a week ago tonight.
从那以后，一切都变得奇怪了
Ever since. everything's been strange.
我唯一需要做的就是挺过记下来的五分钟
All I got to do is make it through the next five minutes.
- 提醒…  - 天呐，不好意思
- As a reminder...  - God. I'm sorry.
- 先生！先生，请待在您的座位上  - 请待在您的座位上
- Sir! Sir. please stay in your seat.  - Please remain in your seats
并系好安全带
with your seat belts fastened.
先生！
Sir!
怎么了？
What was that about?
那个坐在我们旁边的帅哥
That cute guy sitting right next to us...
可能脑袋有点问题
It turns out he's a total head case.
他在跟我说一部将会杀死他的电影
And he was telling me about a movie that's supposed to kill you.
什么电影？
What movie?
一些视频之类的
Some video.
当你看完的时候会有个电话打给你
A chick calls you on the phone after you watch it
还说什么“七天”，好像就是现在
and says. "Seven days." which was. like. right now.
开门
Open up!
你有复制一份吗？
Did you make a copy of it?
你有复制一份录像带吗？
Did you make a copy of the tape?
没有！我…
No! I...
- 女士，安全带的提示灯亮了  - 天呐
- Miss. the seat belt light is on.  - Jesus.
你到底怎么了，这只是个故事
What is going on with you? It's just a story.
我看过它！
I've seen it!
航控中心，我是七十七号客机
Traffic control. this is Flight 77.
我们遭到一些信号干扰
We have some signal interference.
如果你不想买，能不能让一下，我看看
If you're not interested in buying. I'd love to take a look.
好的，可是谁会买这个老式录像带？
Sure. I mean. who would want an old VCR?
想当年它也是一场技术革命
Well. once upon a time this was a technological revolution.
好吧
Okay.
刚刚和那个人讲话
Just talking to the guy.
他所有的东西原来是从
It turns out that he got all this stuff from
一户人家那里拿到的，他们的儿子死于一年前的飞机事故
a family whose son died in a plane crash a couple of years back
现在那些东西已经变成一团过时的垃圾
And now it's just a bunch of outdated junk.
我喜欢用“复古“”这个词来形容
I prefer "vintage."
快啊，你这个老家伙
Come on. old man.
你还有好几年还可以活呢
You still got some life in you.
嘿，Skype？
Hey. Skye?
你猜怎么着
Guess what.
什么？
What?
里面有一个录像带
Had a tape in it.
想知道什么会放出来吗？
Care to see what's down the rabbit hole?
我要上课迟到了
I'm gonna be late for class.
不过你可以一会儿告诉我
But then. maybe you can tell me about it later.
玩的开心，教授
Have fun. Professor.
快点，运转
Come on. work.
你好？
Hello?
七天
Seven days.
什么？你是谁？
What? Who is this?
朱丽亚
Julia.
我一直在想这个故事
I keep thinking about this story.
它简直就像是历史上最浪漫的故事
It's. like. the most romantic story in the history of stories.
是吗，可我们不是这么相遇的
Well. it's not how we met.
不是，这是关于这个男人奥菲斯
No. It's about this guy. Orpheus.
他的女朋友死了，然后他不得不进入地狱来拯救她
His girlfriend dies and he has to literally go down into Hell to rescue her.
为什么一直是男人救女人？
How come it's always the guy rescuing the girl?
因为…
Just...
他一直在寻找她，好吧？最后终于找到了她
He tracks her down. All right? He finds her.
但是恶魔答应让她离开的条件是
And the Devil's gonna let her go on one condition.
他必须在没有女友陪伴的情况下先离开地狱
He has to start first. without her.
他必须先走而且不能回头看她
He has to walk away without looking back at her.
- 但是  - 他忍不住回头瞄了她一眼
- But...  - He looks back to glimpse her
于是，他在第九层地狱永远失去了他的女友
and loses her forever. Ninth grade.
- 英语文学课  - 好吧，原来你懂这个故事
- English Lit.  - Okay. You know it.
所以，你什么意思？
So. what's your point?
我不知道，我只是
I don't know. I just...
在那个男人的处境上想
I relate to the guy.
我简直无法想象能不回头看你
I mean. I can't imagine not looking back at you.
事实上，你必须得走了
Actually. you got to go.
因为我的男朋友要离开这里上大学，而我答应了他帮他收拾行李
Because my boyfriend's leaving for college. and I promised I'd help him pack.
- 不要！ - 来，起床
- No!  - Come on. get up.
宝贝，宝贝，宝贝，他是个失败者，回到床上吧
Baby. baby. baby. he's a loser. Come back to bed.
现在回到床上
Come back to bed. now.
- 你真的需要这些东西？ - 是的
- You really need all this?  - Yeah.
我们走吧，快点，快点
Let's go. Come on. come on.
快点，霍尔特！
Come on. Holt!
我们一小时前就该出发了
Supposed to be on the road an hour ago.
老爸，等我一分钟
Just give us a second. Dad.
你做了一件正确的事
You're doing the right thing.
你的妈妈，她现在真的很需要你
Your mom. she really needs you right now.
我会想念你的气味
I'm gonna miss your smell.
真的？
Really?
真的
Yeah.
好
Okay.
我会在周末的哥伦布纪念日来看你
I'll see you Columbus Day weekend.
还有告诉汤米·隆巴迪，我和他干上了
And tell Tommy Lombardi that I'm on to him.
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
他在我离开的那天得到了一份你公司的工作？
He gets a job where you work the day I leave?
你神经病！
You're crazy!
不要回头看！
Don't look back!
记得今晚九点半Skype视频！
9:30. Skype. tonight!
- 妈的你的衬衫在哪？ - 今晚！
- Where the hell is your shirt?  - Tonight!
- 还有以后的每天晚上！ - 以后的每天晚上！
- And every night!  - And every single night!
除非我和汤米·隆巴迪在一起的时候
Unless I'm with Tommy Lombardi!
你刚刚说什么！
You did not just say that!
宝贝，现在已经六个星期了，我好想你
Baby. it's been six weeks. I can't take it.
为什么你突然变得这么好？因为我们现在不住在一个镇上？
Why are you so much nicer now that we don't live in the same town?
不好意思，你叫什么名字来着？
Sorry. what's your name again?
- 闭嘴  - 那可是个很奇怪的名字
- Shut up.  - That's a weird name.
你上课怎么样？
How are your classes?
有点无聊
Kind of uninspiring.
不过有一门实验生物学课
There's this one Experimental Biology class. though.
那门课的老师有点爱惹是生非
The teacher's kind of a badass.
听起来很有意思
That sounds cool.
是啊
Yeah.
不过不是每件事都有意思
Not everything's cool. though.
感觉就像是过了整整一个星期我才见到你
It's still. like. a whole week until I get to see you.
那么你现在见到我了
Well. you're seeing me now.
是啊，我想是吧
Yeah. I guess.
我现在可以摘下我的发卡吗？
What about I start by taking off my hairclip?
好的，没问题
Yeah. Okay.
然后呢？
What's next?
“带我，带我，我忍不住！”
"Take me. take me. I can't stand it!"
你是怎么进来的？
How did you even get in here?
这些白痴闯进了我的房间
These idiots just broke into my room.
来吧，我们是寻梦之旅，加布里埃尔说你来了
Come on. Vision Quest. Gabriel says you're up.
让我们去第七层
Let's go to the 7s.
- 妈的今晚吗？ - 今晚
- Shit. Tonight?  - Tonight.
抱歉，小姐，你的男朋友今晚有事
Sorry. little lady. but boyfriend's got plans tonight.
- 你知道我们可以聊天  - 我觉得我还好
- You know. but we could talk.  - I think I'm good.
我会补上的，我保证
I'll make it up to you. I promise.
- 我明天就和你说…  - 他会跟你说…
- I'll talk to you tomorrow.  - He'll talk to you...
好的，没问题
Yeah. sure.
我说过我会给你补上的
I told you I'd make it up to you.
朱丽亚…
Julia...
你欠我一个好觉
You owe me a good dream.
- 他在哪？ - 你是谁？
- Where is he?  - Who are you?
霍尔特在哪？
Where's Holt?
我不知道，我已经几天都没有和他说话了
I don't know. I haven't spoken to him in days.
不要对我撒谎！
Don't lie to me!
我没有撒谎！
I'm not lying to you!
你在他的电脑上做什么？
What are you doing on his computer?
告诉他不要再逃，告诉那个死人他逃不了
Tell him there's no hiding. Tell the dead man he can't hide.
什么…你在说什么？你怎么了？
What... What are you talking about? What's wrong with you?
她来了
She's coming.
没有人能够阻止她
There's no stopping her.
告诉霍尔特
Tell Holt that…
请拿起电话
Please pick up the phone.
这是霍尔特，你知道什么…
This is Holt. You know what to…
这是霍尔特，你知道该怎么做
This is Holt. You know what to do.
霍尔特，这是怎么回事？
Holt. what's going on?
我刚刚和那个奇怪的女孩有一段有史以来最奇怪的对话
I just had the strangest conversation in my life with that weird girl.
这是霍尔特，你知道怎么做
This is Holt. You know what to do.
你好？
Hello?
科学告诉过我们，我们仅仅只是
Science has told us that we are merely
由碳和蛋白质构成的原始生物
the primal stirrings of some carbon. some proteins.
我们生活着，可以的时候，
We live a while. eat.
也吃着，做着
have sex. when we can.
这就是生活的全部，直至我们死去
And that's it. then we die.
勒温，这不重要
Lewin. there's no need to take notes on that part.
等一下！
But wait. hold on.
因为没有人否认我们的本体意识
because no one is denying that we have consciousness.
有很多内在的生命没有被解释
Some inner life that's not quite accounted for here.
让我们记住这个邪恶的双重撕裂实验
Let's remember the infamous double-slit experiment.
当没有人看的时候，这些微粒会在同一时间穿过两个缝隙
When no one is watching. the particles just pass through both slits at the same time.
但当观察者在的时候，它们就会表现得向子弹一样
But with an observer. they behave like bullets.
穿过一个或者另一个缝隙
passing through one slit or the other.
朋友，这很重要
This is big. guys.
这非物质的人类意识
The immaterial human consciousness
已经到达并且接触了这里
has reached out and touched the material.
在这个真实的世界上存在可计算的改变
There is a calculable transformation in the real world.
而且仅仅因为
and solely because
有人在这里看着它
someone was there to watch it.
这也解释了
Which may account for the fact
为什么当我发现有一个神秘的陌生人在我房间后面注视着我时
that I have become significantly sweatier once I've noticed
我会汗流浃背
the mysterious stranger watching me from the back of the room.
好吧，就是这样，我们去喝一杯吧
All right. that's it. Go get drunk.
嗨！我记得见过你们…
Hey. I remember you guys from…
- 你为什么会来这里？ - 别这样，哥们
- Why'd you come here?  - Come on. dude.
继续向前，这边请，这边请
Move it along. There you go. There you go.
我能为你做些什么吗？
How can I help you?
我在找我的男朋友
I'm looking for my boyfriend.
他应该在你们这里
He's supposed to be in your class.
好的，请问他叫什么名字？
Okay. What's this guy's name?
霍尔特·安东尼
Holt Anthony.
是的
Yeah.
不确定
Not sure.
我总是要花很多时间，直到感恩节才能弄清楚谁是谁
It always takes me until Thanksgiving to start putting names to faces.
真的吗？
Really? 'Cause
因为我们以为他会为你做一些能取得额外学分的事
he was supposed to do some sort of extra credit thing for you.
他有吗？
Did he?
也许吧，我不知道
Maybe. I don't know.
我知道我还有二十五篇文章要打分
I do know that I have 25 essays to grade.
听着，好吧
Listen. Okay.
对于新学生来说，找到一个比班级更有趣的人或者事
It's not uncommon for a new student to find something or someone
是很罕见的
that's more interesting to them than class.
我可以给你几个忠告吗？往前看
My advice to you? Move on.
- 请你冷静！ - 我告诉你，这是不一样的
- Calm down.  - I'm telling you. it's different.
每个人都这么说，没关系，你的尾巴去哪里了？
Everyone says that. It's okay. Where's your tail?
我再也没有了
I don't have one anymore.
我告诉过你别打给他
I told you not to call him.
那个混蛋挂我电话！
That asshole hung up on me!
我想知道为什么
I wonder why.
好吧，我们来交换尾巴，你和霍尔特说了？
Okay. We'll switch tails. You talk to Holt?
没有！我试过了，他没接电话
No! I tried. He isn't answering his phone.
- 拜托  - 霍尔特有他自己的问题
- Come on.  - Holt has his own problems.
加百列[加布里埃尔]你必须帮助我
You have to help me. Gabriel.
- 都是你的错！你先开始的！ - 请你冷静
- It's your fault! You started this!  - Calm down.
加布，听我说
Listen to me. Gabe!
那些视频，那些尾巴，所有的那些人
The videos. the tails. all these people.
- 这是错的而且她生气了  - 你简直是荒诞不经
- It's wrong and she's pissed!  - You're being ridiculous.
我可以感觉到她，这一切都在改变
I can feel her. It's all changing.
你没有多少时间了，你必须相信我
You don't have much time.You need to trust me.
我该如何才能再次相信你？
How could I ever trust you?
去你的工作室，一路上别和任何人说话
Get to your studio. Don't talk to anyone along the way.
把视频复制下来，然后等我
Make a copy of the video and wait.
我现在就要把它寄给其他人，哎，哎，哎！
I'm gonna send someone right now.Hey. hey. hey!
一切都会好起来的，亲爱的，你能明白吗？
Everything's gonna be fine. darling. You understand?
好的！我知道！
Yes! I understand!
不，你不知道
But you don't.
老实说，我没有找到那段可怕的录像带，但是…
I honestly didn't find the tape to be that scary. but…
哎，你不该出现在这里！
Hey. you're not supposed to be here!
哎！
Hey!
那天晚上你打电话给我
You called me the other night.
哎！看着我
Hey! Look at me.
你是霍尔特的女朋友
You're the girlfriend.
谁是霍尔特？
Where's Holt?
我…我可以帮助你
I... I can help you.
但是我必须要先给你看一样东西
But I need to show you something first.
你住在这里吗？
You live here?
是的，美术，研究生项目
Yeah. Fine Arts. Grad program.
我需要一个清醒的头脑才能做我的工作，以及…我喜欢我的秘密
I need a clear head to do my work and I like my privacy.
霍尔特来过这里吗？
Is Holt even here?
他说过他会在这里吗？
Did I say he would be?
注意脚下，我刚刷了天花板
Be careful where you step I just painted the ceiling.
没有什么问题，他没有在躲你
Nothing's wrong. He's not avoiding you.
他只是正在路上
He's just on a journey.
我想让你看一些东西，然后你会明白的
I want you to watch something and then you'll understand.
- 这是我的手机吗？ - 你在说谎！
- Is that my phone?  - You're lying!
我需要你为我做这个
I need you to do this for me.
这只是一段两分钟的视频，它不会伤害你的
It's just a two-minute video. It won't hurt you.
开门！把门打开！
Open the door!
朱莉娅！我需要你的帮助！
Julia! I need you to help me.
霍尔特看过这个，我们都看过这个
Holt watched it. We've all watched it.
把门打开！
Open the door!
你不是真的
You're not real.
你不是真的！
You're not real!
七点十分
7:10.
我赢了，小婊砸
I win. bitch.
朱勒！
Jules!
发生什么了？发生什么了？！
What happened? What happened?
告诉我你没有看它对吧，告诉我！
Tell me you didn't watch it. Tell me!
她死了！她死了！她死了！[重要的事情说三遍]
She's dead. She's dead. She's dead.
你好？
Hello?
加布里埃尔寄给我的
Gabriel sent me.
我应该要看这个视频
I'm supposed to watch a video.
你好
Hello.
加布里埃尔，加布里埃尔
Gabriel. Gabriel.
你知道斯凯吧？
Do you know about Skye?
我知道，有人在网上放了她的照片
I know. Someone put a picture of her online.
每个人都在退出
Everyone's dropping out.
等一下
Wait.
等一下，你的尾巴现在仍然在？
Wait. Do I still have a tail?
加布里埃尔？
Gabriel?
还有人在看我吗？
Is someone still watching for me?
我会帮你找到人的，我发誓
I'm gonna find you someone. I promise you that.
在原地别动
Just stay where you are.
那是谁
Who was that?
是加布里埃尔
It was Gabriel.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be fine.
这些就是他告诉斯凯的
That's what he told Skye.
听着，朱莉娅
Listen. Julia.
对于你看到的一切，我很抱歉
I'm really sorry that you had to see that.
但是我不能让你也陷入其中
But I can't let you get caught up in this.
我觉得现在这样有点迟了
I think it's a little too late for that.
我看了它
I watched it.
在斯凯之后的十二小时
Twelve hours after Skye.
我们应该通过这个帮助对方
We were supposed to help each other through it.
帮助对方？
"Help each other"?
是的
Yeah.
- 所以你和她…  - 不
- So were you and her…  - No.
加布里埃尔说，我们当中的一部分人会被选中加入这个实验
Gabriel said a few of us were gonna be chosen for this experiment.
如果你听过他描述它的方式
If you just heard the way he described it.
我们可以证实人死后
That we could prove the existence of a soul.
灵魂的存在
Of life after death.
我知道，我知道，这听上去很荒谬
I know. I know. It sounds crazy.
但我只是…
but I'm just…
这个磁带是一扇门通往另一边
The tape is the doorway to the other side.
那，为什么她死了？
Then why did she die?
在你死前，你有七天时间
You have seven days before you die.
你不得不看这份磁带并且复制一份，然后给别的人看
You just have to watch the tape and make a copy. and show it to someone else.
然后你就会没事
And then you're fine.
加布里埃尔把它称作一条“尾巴”
Gabriel calls it a "tail."
她没有把她的尾巴给别人看
Her tail just didn't show.
所以你原本想将死刑判决传递给别人？
So were you supposed to pass on a death sentence to someone else?
你是怎么卷入其中的？
How could you get involved in this?
求你了
Please.
无论你是什么
Whatever you are.
离他远点
leave him alone.
七天
Seven days.
朱勒，你做了什么
Jules. What did you do?
我看到了一些东西
I saw something.
那有一间房间，一扇门
There was a room. A door.
- 是的  - 那是加布里埃尔
- Yeah.  - It's Gabriel.
霍尔特，听着，我给你找了一件燕尾服
Holt. listen. I've got a tail for you.
这将不再属于我
It's not for me anymore
你应该我知道为什么我不接你的电话吧，对吗？
You know why I wasn't answering your calls. right?
这是为了保护你
It was to protect you from this.
加布里埃尔帮我想了个解决办法
Gabriel had a solution for me.
一切都会好的，我也会好的
It would have been fine. I would have been fine.
那么我也会好的
Then I'll be fine. too.
朱勒！
Jules!
发生了什么？
What happened?
一只鸟
A bird.
刚刚那有只鸟
There was a bird.
朱丽娅
Julia!
看到了吗？我都说了那有只鸟
See? I told you there was a bird.
朱丽娅！
Julia!
但我看到了它
But I saw it.
所以，你看了那卷磁带嘛
So. you watched the tape.
我需要像神话一样祭祀自己吗
And I had dismissed self-sacrifice as popular myth.
霍尔特已经快没有时间了
Holt was running out of time.
这是唯一可以救他的办法了
It was the only way to save him.
每个人都需要完成它
Anyone would have done it.
你知道的，我可以向你展示一些调查
You know. I could show you some research
会显示出相反的结果
that would suggest the opposite.
她已经做了决定
She's marked already.
在第一天
On day one.
但这，这是不同的
And it's... It's different.
直到第五天我也还没决定
I wasn't marked until day five.
加布里埃尔，这一定有着什么含义
Gabriel. this has to mean something.
这一切发生的太快了
It's happening faster.
可能所有一些都变了
Maybe it is all changing.
我相信这卷磁带一定代表了一些事情
I wanted to believe that tape meant a lot of things.
当我们死亡的时候
That our souls are eternal.
我们的灵魂未灭
and when we die.
灵魂在试图寻找一个新的家
the spirit strives to find a new home.
然后我看到了那个图片
Then I saw the picture.
我看到了斯凯的脸
I saw Skye's face.
你也看到了
You saw it. too.
为了活下来，你复制了一份，然后给别人看了
You want to survive. you make a copy and you show someone.
如果不是你，根本不会有人死亡
No one is dying because of me.
我告诉他们这个是怎么回事
I'll tell them how it works.
所以呢？诅咒还是会继续吗
And so what? The cycle just continues?
你觉得怎么样才能活下来
What do you think survival is?
赶快去复印一份
Just make a copy.
我们再决定待会怎么做
We'll decide what to do with it later.
拜托了
Please.
你刚在这里干什么
What did you do here?
她的版本没办法复印
Her version won't copy.
什么叫做“没办法复印”？
What do you mean "it won't copy"?
你的文件比一般的要大
Your file size is larger than the original.
怎么可能呢
How can that be?
擦拭一下她的复印件
Scrub through her copy.
这是什么，快回去
What is that? Go back.
在这里！
Right there!
那只鸟
The bird.
我都告诉你了我在车里见过那只鸟
I told you in the car I saw that bird.
什么？
What?
它不应该在这里
It shouldn't be there.
我需要我的设备
I need my equipment.
好吧，看到了吗，有些奇怪的断口在那些数字编码里
Okay. See. there's these weird gaps in the digital code.
差错，我们在哪里找到的那些灵魂的图像，就像你的鸟
Glitches where we get these ghost images. like your bird.
我的意思是，我们在讨论一个或者两个帧的静止图像
I mean. we're talking one or two frame still images.
但那明明有更多的图像
but there's more.
那有视频数据浓缩在这些静止帧之中
There's video data condensed in the still frames.
有一个视频在这个视频里面？
A video within the video?
嗯哼，你看
Well. there is now.
我不希望你看这个
I don't want you to watch it.
朱勒，我们没有别的办法了
Jules. there's no way.
别再说了，我们一起看这个
We're watching this together. End of discussion.
霍尔特，无论如何，我觉得这是针对朱莉娅一个人的
Holt. whatever it is. I think it's intended for Julia alone.
看着我
Look at me.
我知道，你很不开心，因为我看了这个视频
I know you're upset that I watched it.
但是我们不能任由它徒然地去
But we can't let it be for nothing.
所以，不要回头看，好吗？
So don't look back. okay?
把它放好
Put it on.
朱勒？
Jules?
亲爱的，告诉我们你看到了什么
Baby. tell us what you see.
一个钟
A clock.
一个在洪水之中的十字架
A cross in a flood.
一个女孩
A girl.
朱勒
Jules.
朱勒？
Jules?
我不知道
I don't know.
一具燃烧的尸体
A burning body.
朱勒！
Jules!
对不起，我…
Sorry. I…
那个是什么？
What was it?
只是图片而已，但我无法解释那种感觉
Only images. but I can't explain how it felt.
洪水，火焰，火葬[火化]
Flood. Fire. Cremation.
这些图片从来之前从没有在磁带上出现过
Those are images that have never been on the tape before.
你知道的吧，原始文化相信只有一种方法能让灵魂获得自由
You know. primitive cultures believed that the only way to free a soul
那就是焚烧尸体
is to burn the body.
换而言之，如果你能找到它
That is. if you can find it.
等一下
Wait.
我见过这个
I saw this.
那个地方，是他们焚烧她尸体的地方
That's where they buried her.
那是一座城，叫做圣礼城
I traced it to a town called Sacrament Valley.
离这里有大概四个小时的路程
about four hours from here.
那里就是我们需要去的地方
That's where we need to go.
你在听吗？
Hello?
谢谢你，贾马尔
Thank you. Jamal.
警察正在来的路上
The police are on their way here.
你不愿意跟我们一块走吗？
And you're not even coming with us!
霍尔特，警察想要问我一些问题
The police want to ask me questions. Holt.
- 他们觉得是你杀了斯凯  - 但是你没有
- They think you killed Skye.  - But you didn't.
我真希望你从义务教育中学到过什么
I hope if you learn anything from an education.
那就是，不止一个理论可以是真的
it's that more than one theory can be true.
我没有杀斯凯
I didn't kill Skye.
或者，是我做的
And I did.
但是警察从不接受摸棱两可
But the cops don't deal in such ambiguities.
这是我的我的调查
My research.
所有关于这个磁带的资料都在这
Everything that's known about the tape is in there.
它们比我对你更有用
It'll be more of a help to you than I can be.
一个从没达到过工作标准的男人
A man never quite measures up to his work.
这些在磁带上的图片是她的故事
The images on the tape. they were her story.
她希望这些故事能被知晓
She wanted it to be heard.
萨马拉曾经是一个被遗弃的孤儿
"Samara was found abandoned as a young child.
没有人知道她从哪里来，没人知道她的父母是谁
"No one knew where she came from or who her parents were.
于是大家意识到她是被遗弃的
"She was adopted. and they realized
关于这个女孩的一些事情很反常
"that something was unnatural about this girl.
一些邪恶的事情
"Something evil.
他们试图杀了她
"They tried to kill her.
“但萨马拉在井底幸存了七天”
"but Samara survived for seven days at the bottom of the well.
“他们几年后发现了她的尸体”
"They found her body years later."
他们把她一路带到这个城镇呢？
And they brought her all the way to this town?
为什么？
Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
那个女孩
That girl.
什么女孩？
What girl?
你好！
Hello?
- 我能帮你吗？ - 嘿…
- Can I help you?  - Hey...
快天黑了，请问你们还有空房吗？
There was no light outside. Do you have any vacancies?
两个房间？
Two rooms?
一个
One.
只收现金，在中午结帐
Cash only. Checkout's at noon.
这是非常旧的房间
It's an old house.
墙壁很薄
Walls are thin.
希望你不介意的有猫
Hope you don't mind the cats.
我刚刚在大厅里
I'm just down the hall.
打扰一下，这张照片中的女孩是谁？
Excuse me. Who's the girl in this photo?
中间的那个？
The one in the middle there?
什么？那是我的侄女
Why. that's my niece.
很漂亮，对吧？人们说我们看起来…
Beautiful. isn't she? People say we look just…
不，我很抱歉，我是说拿着小提琴的女孩
No. I'm sorry. I meant the girl with the violin.
那是伊夫林
That's Evelyn.
我想我看到她了
I think I saw her.
在今天早些时候
Earlier today.
这是不可能的
That's not possible.
她三十年前就消失了
She disappeared 30 years ago.
有人知道为什么吗
Does anyone know why?
不知道
No.
我不想谈这个
And I'd rather not talk about it.
女士，教会在哪里？
Ma'am. where's the church?
这里没有教会了
Well. it's not a church anymore.
那是当我撞到石头底部
That's when I hit rock bottom.
我猜最糟糕的部分，是我放弃了我的孩子
I guess the worst part of it for me was that I let down my kids.
放弃了我的丈夫
I let down my husband.
如果生活让你失望，请举起手来
Raise your hand if life ever let you down.
现在去吧，举起你的手
Go ahead now. raise your hand.
然后你发现了这毒品，以为得到了解脱
And then you found the drug that you thought unlocked a secret.
今天就到这吧
One day at a time.
谢谢大家的光临
Thank you all for coming.
下周再见
I'll see you next week.
朱勒，我们最好走吧
Jules. We better go.
所以，我们现在干什么？
So. what do we do now?
刚来这的年轻人，不要让它杀了你
Awful young to be here. Don't let it kill you.
打扰一下，先生！
Excuse me. sir!
关于教会你能告诉我一点点吗？
Could you tell me a little bit more about the church?
什么时候关闭？
When did it close?
已经十三年了
Been 13 years.
在被淹没之前
After the flood.
这个小镇曾经的人口是现在的五倍
Town used to have five times this many people.
从那时到现在
Ever since.
死神的镰刀比降临的生命来得更快
there's more dead than alive around here.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 他说这个教堂以前…  - 这就是曾经他们带她来的地方
- He said the church was…  - That's where they brought her.
这个墓地
The cemetery.
去找她的名字
Look for her name.
拜托，快接电话
Come on. pick up.
这是霍尔特，你知道该做什么
This is Holt. You know what to do.
霍尔特，我是加布里埃尔
Holt. it's Gabriel.
我不知道你是否拿到了这些信息
I don't know if you're getting these messages.
但我已经知道了朱丽亚手上的标记代表着什么
but I figured outBut I can't let you get caught up in this. the mark on Julia's hand.
那个是盲文，我马上过来找你们
It's braille. I'm gonna come find you guys.
觉醒的水会带着他们安全地回到上帝身边
"The waters rose to carry them and brought them back safely to God."
霍尔特！
Holt!
哎，哎，哎
Hey. hey. hey.
她在那
She's in there.
有人动了她
Someone moved her.
朱勒？
Jules?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
这里有字
There's writing.
霍尔特
Holt.
霍尔特！
Holt!
朱莉娅！
Julia!
嘿，发生什么了？发生什么了？发生什么了？
Hey. what happened? What happened? What happened?
我看见了一些东西
I saw something.
那个井
The well.
- 我们只是在找…  - 我知道你们在找什么
- We were just looking…  - I know who you're looking for.
走吧
Let's go.
- 你找到了什么？ - 两个孩子
- What did you find?  - Two kids.
看到他们从二九四号破门而入
Caught them breaking into 294.
破门而入？
Breaking in?
好吧，真新鲜
Well. that's new.
要不要把他们带到警长办公室？
You want me to take them down to the Sheriff's Office?
不不不不不不，不要麻烦警长了
No. no. no. no. no. don't bother the Sheriff.
我会照顾好这一切
I can take care of this.
我是盖伦·伯克
I'm Galen Burke.
我在这里做看守
I watch over things here.
可以这么说
So to speak.
请进
Please. Come in.
这不算什么
It's not much.
但我不曾期待过陪伴
But I wasn't expecting company.
- 我…我可以…  - 不，不用了，我没事，孩子
- I can... I can take…  - No. no. I'm fine. son.
我对这房子了如指掌
I know every corner of this house.
所以
So.
你在寻找一位女孩
you're looking for the girl.
真有意思
I find it interesting
你竟在她的标记移走后还能找到她的坟墓
that you managed to find her grave even after the marker was removed.
我做过一个梦
I had a vision.
梦里有一张坟墓的地图，它想领着我去那
An image of that grave that led me here.
在坟墓的里面
And inside the grave.
我看见了一个井
I saw a vision of a well.
一个幻象
A vision.
所以，你想要知道关于萨马拉·摩根的事情
So. you want to know about Samara Morgan.
我们的牧师非常积极
Our priest was very active with the community back then.
他听说那个小女孩
He heard that after all the little girl had been through
曾经被长眠之地拒绝过
that she was being denied a resting place.
好吧，谁说的宽容不意味着死亡呢？
Well. who's to say that charity isn't meant for the dead?
那么，为什么她现在不在这里？
So why isn't she there now?
因为我们为这种宽容的行为付清了代价
Well. because we paid mightily for this act of charity.
就好像上帝和大自然本身想让我们摆脱她
It was as if God and nature itself wanted us to be rid of her.
- 那个洪水  - 是的
- The flood.  - Yes.
但是我需要让自己
But I had let myself believe.
像你一样
like you.
相信她试图想告诉我什么
that she was trying to tell me something.
我曾被拉向坟墓
I was pulled to that grave.
她给我看了一些东西
She showed me things.
一些没有人可以想象到的东西
Things that no one should have to imagine.
然后我就失去了理智
And then I went blind.
- 对不起  - 不，不用说对不起
- I'm so sorry.  - No. don't be.
它给我带来了宁静
It brought me peace.
那个牧师要求移动她的尸体
The priest requested that her body be moved.
他离开了圣礼城[Sacrament Valley]
He left Sacrament Valley.
她被埋在了城市北边的波特墓园
She was buried in a potter's field just north of town.
被所有人遗忘
to be forgotten by all.
我觉得我们需要出去
I think we should get out of here.
听我说
Listen to me.
那个女孩不值得我们好奇
There is nothing about that girl that's worth being curious about.
我需要了解这一切
I need to see this through.
为什么
Why?
因为你认为被选择是有原因的吗？
Because you think you were chosen for something?
你有一个梦境不代表你知道那个梦境代表着什么
Having a vision doesn't mean you know what that vision means.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你手上有什么东西？
What's this on your hand?
为什么你要把这个标记放在手上？
Why did you put this mark on your hand?
你这是什么意思？
What do you mean?
小心
Be careful.
记住了？
You hear me?
所以，现在我们要干什么？
So. what now?
我们需要找到那具尸体
We gotta find the body.
- 啥？ - 你，在这别动
- What?  - Hey. stay right there.
这条路关闭了，刚刚发生了事故
This road's closed. There's been an accident.
- 你们需要掉头  - 好的，警官
- Need you to turn it around.  - Okay. sir.
- 朱丽亚！ - 是那个女孩
- Julia!  - It's that girl.
图中的那个女孩
From the picture.
哎，你想往哪走呢，先生？
Hey! Where do you think you're going. sir?
请你掉头
Excuse me. Turn around.
停下！
Stop!
伊夫林！
Evelyn!
你给我停下！
Stop!
加布里埃尔？
Gabriel?
加布里埃尔
Gabriel.
- 在这里！他需要帮助！ - 哎！
- Over here! He needs help!  - Hey!
加布里埃尔
Gabriel.
这是什么
What is it?
嘿，先生！拜托！
Hey. sir! Please!
加布里埃尔，告诉我
Gabriel. tell me.
你不能下去！
You can't be down there!
朱丽亚！
Julia!
他来这是有理由的
He was coming for a reason.
他想告诉我们一些事情
He wanted to tell us something.
不，是她想要告诉我们一些事情
No. she wanted to tell us something.
这个女孩有一些关于萨马拉的事情
This girl has something to do with Samara.
我们必须回去
We need to go back.
我能感觉到她的痛苦，她的经历
I can feel her pain. her suffering.
我有些心烦意乱，而且感觉越来越糟
I'm sick with it and it's getting worse.
我很累了
I'm so tired.
那你睡吧
Then you sleep.
我准备给咱俩弄些吃的
I'm gonna get us something to eat.
好的
Okay.
看
Look.
我们会想到办法的
We'll figure this out.
我当时就在那里
I was right there.
吃的来了，凯伦
There you go. Karen.
炸鸡，肉排，还有咖啡
Chicken fried steak and coffee.
嘿，菜单？
Hey. Menu?
是的！当然
Yeah. Sure.
嗯，那是什么？鸡肉或者牛排？
So. what is that? Chicken or steak?
你真有意思
You're funny.
听着，我…
Look. I…
我无意冒犯，但是…
I don't mean to be rude. but…
你侄女的朋友，那个消失不见的女生…
The girl who's friends with your niece. the one who disappeared…
你能和我说一点到底发生了什么吗？
Can you tell me a little bit more about what happened?
我侄女和她通过教堂的音乐项目互相认识的
My niece and she knew each other through the church music program.
但她是最有天赋的
But she was the most gifted.
人们经常和她开玩笑：“这里是小庙，容不下你”
People used to kid her. "You're too good for this place.
“等有一天，当我们醒过来，你就会消失了，嗯，一定会这样的”
"We're gonna wake up one day and you'll be gone. and that'll be that."
我觉得这种玩笑开不得，
I guess there's certain jokes you shouldn't make
因为，它真的会发生的
because it happened.
她真的失踪了
She disappeared.
一件衣服也没有留下，也没有留下什么话
No clothes gone. No note.
就那样凭空消失了
Just vanished.
当时的牧师，
The priest.
他把你关在这里
He kept you down here.
这个孩子！
The child!
三十四周
Thirty-four weeks.
八个半月
Eight and a half months.
你当时怀孕了
You were pregnant.
你是萨马拉的妈妈
You were Samara's mother.
警察调查了六个月，然后就没有消息了
The police investigated for six months. and then we stopped hearing from them.
从那之后，感觉镇子就不太对了
Town never felt quite the same after that.
那个牧师
The priest.
你知道他发生了什么吗？
Do you know what happened to him?
他还住在镇上
He still lives in town.
虽然他早就不是牧师了
Although he isn't a priest anymore.
自从他瞎了之后就不是了
Not since he went blind.
我要走了，不好意思
I have to go. Excuse me.
伯克先生！
Mr. Burke!
是朱丽亚！我必须和你谈一谈！
It's Julia! I have to talk to you!
那个男孩不和你在一起
The boy's not with you.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我想我理解我看到的了
I think I understand my visions.
她所展示给我的事情
The things she's been showing me.
我需要了解一下那个牧师
I need to know about the priest.
我猜，就像镇里的大多人一样，
I guess. just like most people in the town.
这件事情使他身体被掏空
the event sort of took it out of him.
只是我不能理解为什么
I just don't see why it matters.
三十年前在这里消失的女孩
There was a girl here 30 years ago who disappeared.
我见过她
I've seen her.
伊夫林·伯顿
Evelyn Borden.
你认识她？
You knew her?
大家都认识伊夫林
Everyone knew Evelyn.
她被关在教堂下面
She was kept under the church.
我找到了一个房间，就像监狱一样
I found a room. It was like a prison.
在墙上有天数的标记
There were days marked off on the walls.
九个月
Nine months.
她萨马拉的妈妈
She's Samara's mother.
从她出生起就她就饱受痛苦
She suffered from the day she was born.
并且这种痛苦持续到现在
And she's still suffering now.
我觉得我理解了
I think I understand it.
这是诅咒，这
This curse. This.
除非她自由，否则永远不会结束的
It will never stop until she's free.
是什么声音？
What's that sound?
蝉？
Cicadas.
伯克
Burke.
朱勒？
Jules?
朱勒
Jules!
朱丽亚…
Julia...
我知道被幻象所带领是什么感觉
I know what it's like to be guided by visions.
准确而言，
To be certain.
我曾确信我将成为
I was certain that I would father
可以改变世界的孩子的父亲
a child that was gonna change the world.
我是对的
And I was right.
你看，朱丽亚
You see. Julia.
她并没有夺取我的视力
she didn't take my sight.
是我自己
I did.
好姑娘
Good girl.
- 你非常的勇敢  - 你是萨马拉的父亲！
- You're very brave.  - You're Samara's father.
你绑架了伊夫林
You kidnapped Evelyn.
我和她睡在一起的那晚
The night that I laid with her.
我听见了它们
I heard them.
蝉鸣
The cicadas.
你移动了她的骨头，并且她依然被你囚禁着
You moved her bones and she's still your prisoner.
彼此彼此
As are you.
你以为你是她哭喊要求放了她的
You think that you're the first Good Samaritan
第一个好心人吗？
that she cried out to. to free her?
你是第十二个，朱丽亚
You're the 12th. Julia.
虽然其他人没有像你这样挖的这么深
Though none of the others got this far.
你觉得你很快就会给她带来平静了
You think that you're so close to bringing her peace.
但是你不知道，你将会被流放到地狱
But you have no idea the hell that you would unleash on the world.
朱丽亚？
Julia?
萨马拉不会伤害我的，因为我看不见她
Samara can't hurt me because I can't see her.
但是你，朱丽亚
But you. Julia.
我可以听见你的每一次呼吸
I can hear your every breath!
你无法
You will
使她得到自由！
not set her free!
朱丽亚
Julia.
你让我想起了伊夫林
you remind me of Evelyn.
我曾经用链条锁住过她的双手
I chained Evelyn's hands
因为她曾试图杀掉我们的孩子
because she was trying to kill our child.
我应该让她去的！
I should have let her!
她曾是你的女儿！
She was your daughter!
你想告诉我什么？
What are you trying to show me?
不要
No.
萨马拉
Samara.
你在这
You're here.
朱莉娅
Julia?
她在这，萨马拉
Here she is. Samara!
这就是你的救世主！
This is what becomes of your savior!
带着圣灵的恩典
With the grace of the Holy Spirit.
请让主将你从罪恶之中
may the Lord who freed you from sin
拯救出来
save you.
带你去天堂
and raise you up!
朱莉娅…
Julia…
别离开我
Don't leave me.
…从罪恶之中！
...from sin!
请让主拯救你！
May the Lord save you!
通过这样圣洁的洗礼…
Through this holy anointing…
谁在那？
Who's there?
萨马拉
Samara.
嘿，没事的
Hey. It's okay.
都结束了
It's over.
还没
Not yet.
那是一种什么感觉？
What could that have felt like?
对所有应该爱你的人感到畏惧
To be feared by everyone who's supposed to love you.
并不是所有人
Not everyone.
你从没怕过她
You were never afraid of her.
你自由了，萨马拉
You're free. Samara.
霍尔特，那是加布里埃尔
Holt. It's Gabriel.
我不知道你是否收到过这些信息
I don't know if you're getting these messages.
但是我知道朱莉娅手上的记号代表着什么了
but I figured out the mark on Julia's hand.
那是盲文，我会回来找你们的
It's braille. I'm gonna come find you guys.
我们的灵魂是不朽的
Our souls are eternal.
当我们死去
and when we die.
我们的心灵会去寻找到一个新的归宿
the spirit strives to find a new home.
我要告诉你，她回来了
I'm telling you. she's coming back.
这次是真的
This time for real.
你再也不会害怕她了
You were never afraid of her.
仅仅因为你有过一个梦境
Just because you had a vision
不代表你知道那个梦境代表什么
doesn't mean you know what that vision means.
你根本不知道
You have no idea
那个你将会被流放去的地狱
the hell that you would unleash on the world.
对不起
And I'm sorry.
它不会停止的
It won't stop.
不，不要
No. no.
什么
What?
不，不要，不要！
No. no. no!
停下！
Stop!
拜托！
Come on!
重生
rebirth
朱莉娅
Julia!